Step 1: click (576, 571) [OK]\NI can see the GitHub trending page is already loaded. There are several trending repositories visible on the screen. The
Step 2: click (576, 571) [OK]\NLooking at the current screenshot, I can see the GitHub trending page is already displayed. The task asks me to scroll d
Step 3: scroll  [OK]\NI can see I'm on a GitHub repository page (alibaba/zvec), not the GitHub trending page. The task asks me to scroll down
Step 4: click (253, 72) [OK]\NI can see I'm currently on a GitHub repository page (alibaba/zvec), not the GitHub trending page. The task asks me to sc
Step 5: click (153, 72) [OK]\NI can see I'm currently on a GitHub repository page (alibaba/zvec). The task asks me to scroll down to see trending repo
Step 6: click (267, 72) [OK]\NI can see I'm currently on the GitHub repository page for alibaba/zvec. The task asks me to scroll down to see trending
Step 7: click (1902, 121) [OK]\NI can see I'm currently on the GitHub repository page for alibaba/zvec. The task asks me to scroll down to see trending
Step 8: click (279, 72) [OK]\NI can see I'm currently on the GitHub repository page for alibaba/zvec. The task asks me to scroll down to see trending
Step 9: click (66, 28) [OK]\NI can see I'm currently on the GitHub repository page for alibaba/zvec. The task asks me to scroll down to see trending
Step 10: click (66, 28) [OK]\NI can see I'm currently on the GitHub repository page for alibaba/zvec. The task asks me to scroll down to see trending
Step 11: click (66, 28) [OK]\NI can see I'm currently on the GitHub repository page for alibaba/zvec. The task asks me to scroll down to see trending
Step 12: click (960, 72) [OK]\NI can see I'm on the GitHub repository page for alibaba/zvec. The task asks me to scroll down to see trending repositori